<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GlowGuide</string>
    <string name="info">About the Application</string>
    <string name="page1">Analyze your skin</string>
    <string name="page2">Product Recommendations</string>
    <string name="page3">Care Routine</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
    <string name="intro">Welcome to GlowGuide😊! Your faithful companion on your beauty and skincare journey. Start your beauty journey now and discover the natural glow you\'ve been dreaming of!</string>
    <string name="intro">Selamat datang di GlowGuide😊! Teman setia Anda dalam perjalanan kecantikan dan perawatan kulit. Mulai perjalanan kecantikan Anda sekarang dan temukan kilau alami yang Anda impikan!</string>
    <string name="image_jenis_kulit">Analyze your skin</string>
    <string name="image_product_skincare">Product Recommendations</string>
    <string name="image_skincare_routine">Care Routines</string>
    <string name="info_aplikasi">GlowGuide app is an app that helps users to know their skin type, provides advice on suitable and avoidable ingredients in skincare, recommends suitable products and provides an optimal skincare routine based on skin type. So the main features are as follows:\n\n1. Analyze Your Skin\n2. Product Recommendation\n3. Care Routine</string>
    <string name="info_aplikasi">GlowGuide app is an app that helps users to know their skin type, provides advice on suitable and avoidable ingredients in skincare, recommends suitable products and provides an optimal skincare routine based on skin type. So the main features are as follows:  1. Analyze Your Skin 2. Product Recommendation 3. Care Routine</string>
    <string name="intro_jenis_kulit">Want to know what skincare is right for your skin type? Try it now!</string>
    <string name="nama">Your Name</string>
    <string name="jenis_kulit">Your Skin Type</string>
    <string name="kulit_normal">Normal Skin</string>
    <string name="kulit_kering">Dry Skin</string>
    <string name="kulit_berminyak">Oily Skin</string>
    <string name="kulit_kombinasi">Combination Skin</string>
    <string name="komplikasi_kulit">Want to add complications?</string>
    <string name="komedo_putih">Whitehead</string>
    <string name="komedo_hitam">Blackheads</string>
    <string name="jerawat">Acne</string>
    <string name="keriput">Wrinkles</string>
    <string name="input_invalid">Must not be empty</string>
    <string name="kulit_invalid">Must choose skin type</string>
    <string name="cek_hasil">Check Result</string>
    <string name="reset">Clear</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_kulit_normal">1. Exfoliating acids and enzymes\n2. Retinoids\n3. Vitamin C\n4. Hyaluronic acid\n5. Polyglutamic Acid</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_kulit_kering">1. Alpha hydroxy acids (AHAs)\n2. Enzyme exfoliants\n3. Retinoids\n4. Vitamin C\n5. Hyaluronic acid and Polyglutamic acid\n6. Ceramides</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_kulit_kombinasi">1. Exfoliating acids\n2. Retinoids\n3. Vitamin C\n4. Enzyme exfoliants\n5. Hyaluronic acid and Polyglutamic acid\n6. Niacinamide</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_komplikasi_keriput">1. Exfoliating acids\n2. Vitamin C\n3. Hyaluronic acid and Polyglutamic acid\n4. Peptides\n5. Niacinamide</string>
    <string name="header_hasil">Analysis Result</string>
    <string name="header_hasil">Analysis Result</string>
    <string name="sapaan">Hallo %s 😊</string>
    <string name="hasil_analisis">\nAfter analyzing with the info you provided below:</string>
    <string name="jenis_kulit_label">"Skin Type: "</string>
    <string name="komplikasi_label">"Complications: "</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_jenis_kulit">\nSkincare ingredient recommendations according to skin type:</string>
    <string name="hindari_jenis_kulit">\nAvoid skincare ingredients according to skin type:</string>
    <string name="rekomendasi_komplikasi">\nRekomendasi bahan skincare sesuai komplikasi kulit:</string>
    <string name="intro_rekomendasi">GlowGuide provides information on what products are being recommended!</string>
    <string name="sabun_muka">1. Facial Wash</string>
    <string name="sabun_muka_deskripsi">It contains oat, heartleaf, collagen, and real green tea leaves that can clean your face from dirt, dust, air pollution, and makeup residue that is still left on your face after outdoor activities. Even though it can deep cleanse your face, this face wash won\'t give you a tugging effect, instead your face will feel softer and more moisturized! This face wash is also suitable for those with sensitive and acne prone skin types.</string>
    <string name="toner_muka">2. Facial Toner</string>
    <string name="toner_muka_deskripsi">After washing your face with a face wash, the next step in your skincare ritual is to use a toner. Yup, using a toner can help your skin absorb the next skincare product better. Well, this toner from Dear Klairs can provide maximum moisture for your skin, balance your skin\'s pH, and most importantly, it can also relieve irritation on your skin.</string>
    <string name="serum_muka">3. Face Serum</string>
    <string name="serum_muka_deskripsi">Looking for a serum that can help your skin look brighter and soothe acne scars? You should put Avoskin Your Skin Bae Serum Alpha Arbutin 3% + Grapeseed on your skincare wish list! This serum combines the active ingredients Alpha Arbutin 3% and extracts from grapeseed. With the combination of the two, you can achieve bright-looking skin. Plus, the antioxidant-rich grapeseed also has a role to keep your skin cells feeling and looking healthier!</string>
    <string name="masker_muka">4. Face Mask</string>
    <string name="masker_muka_deskripsi">Regularly using an exfoliating mask can help to remove dead skin cells, so your skin will feel cleaner. One of the most popular exfoliating masks is the Whitelab Mugwort Pore Clarifying Mask. With tea tree, this mask will control the excess oil present on your face and help to reduce the appearance of acne too, if you use it regularly. Plus, it contains BHA to remove dead skin cells!</string>
    <string name="intro_rutinitas">To keep your skin healthy, fresh and shiny. You must remember this daily routine!</string>
    <string name="judul_rutinitas">Skincare Usage Sequence</string>
    <string name="skincare_pagi">Morning skincare routine</string>
    <string name="urutan_pagi">1. Facial cleanser\n2. Toner\n3. Serum\n4. Moisturizer\n5. Sunscreen</string>
    <string name="skincare_malam">Night skincare routine</string>
    <string name="urutan_malam">1. Double Cleansing\n2. Toner\n3. Serum\n4. Moisturizer\n5. Eye Cream\n6. Retinol</string>
</resources>